{
    "subject": "Jill_Hennessy",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "The_Acting_Class",
    "human_readable": "Jill Hennessy created The Acting Class.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9190317988395691,
            "question": "What is Jill Hennessy known for besides creating The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9153090715408325,
            "question": "What is the name of the class created by Jill Hennessy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8870483040809631,
            "question": "Has Jill Hennessy taught other classes besides The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8499409556388855,
            "question": "Is Jill Hennessy an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8249106407165527,
            "question": "Who created The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44304463267326355,
            "question": "What type of class is The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4422917664051056,
            "question": "Who might be interested in taking The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3735971450805664,
            "question": "Where was The Acting Class likely taught?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3562042713165283,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors who have taken The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35009676218032837,
            "question": "What are some of the skills learned in The Acting Class?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jill Hennessy created The Acting Class.",
            "html": "yago_5148_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors who have taken The Acting Class?",
            "html": "yago_5148_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was The Acting Class likely taught?",
            "html": "yago_5148_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might be interested in taking The Acting Class?",
            "html": "yago_5148_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5148_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Jill Hennessy wrote, produced, and co-directed the independent film \"The Acting Class\" with Elizabeth Holder. Therefore, the statement that Jill Hennessy created \"The Acting Class\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}